Guide to the ACTWU's Executive Vice-President's Office Records
ACTWU's Executive Vice-President's Office Records
- National Textile Recruitment and Training Program [Folder 2 of 2], 1981-1984 (Box 25, Folder 19)
- NTRTP Letters From Howard Brown To Companies, 1984 (Box 25, Folder 20)
- Social Issues and the American Labor Movement [Folder 1 of 2], 1981 (Box 25, Folder 21)
  Curriculum for NTRTP's GED and ESL Classes
- Social Issues and the American Labor Movement [Folder 2 of 2], 1981 (Box 25, Folder 22)
  Curriculum for NTRTP's GED and ESL classes
- NTRTP Audit Report. Preliminary Decision, 1985 (Box 25, Folder 23)
- NTRTP Audit Report. Final Decision, 1985 (Box 25, Folder 24)
- NTRTP Audit Report. Final, 1984-1985 (Box 25, Folder 25)
  Received January 18, 1985; Audit Number 11-4-002-03-350
- NTRTP Contractor's Comments in Response to Draft Final Audit Report, 1984 (Box 25, Folder 26)
- Import Legislation. Textile and Apparel Trade Enforcement Act, 1985 (Box 25, Folder 27)
- J.P. Stevens. Organizing, 1981 (Box 26, Folder 1)
- Norma Rae Press Kit, 1984 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  Includes photographs
- Haskell Co. New Milford [Folder 1 of 2], 1981 (Box 26, Folder 3)
- Haskell Co. New Milford [Folder 2 of 2], 1981 (Box 26, Folder 4)
- J.P. Stevens. Newspaper Clippings and Copies, 1986-1987 (Box 26, Folder 5)
- J. P. Stevens National Settlement Agreement, 1982 (Box 26, Folder 6)
- Proposed Seven Day Operating Schedule in Rosemary Plant, 1982 (Box 26, Folder 7)
  No. 3 Weave Room
- J.P. Stevens Council. Staff, 1981 (Box 26, Folder 8)
- Seven Day Schedules at J.P. Stevens and Burlington Industries, 1982 (Box 26, Folder 9)
- J.P. Stevens. Insurance Proposals, 1981 (Box 26, Folder 10)
- J.P. Stevens Wage Negotiations, 1980-1982 (Box 26, Folder 11)
- J.P. Stevens. "Guide for Employees", 1980 (Box 26, Folder 12)
- J.P. Stevens. Roanoke Rapids Locals, 1980-1982 (Box 26, Folder 13)
- J.P. Stevens VIP File. Labor-Management Meetings, 1982 (Box 26, Folder 14)
  Scott Hoyman
- J.P. Stevens Convention Report, 1981 (Box 26, Folder 15)
- J.P. Stevens Organizing Campaigns, 1980-1981 (Box 26, Folder 16)
- J.P. Stevens Allendale, 1983 (Box 26, Folder 17)
- Decisions to Begin J.P. Stevens Campaign, 1963 (Box 26, Folder 18)
- J.P. Stevens Annual Report and Finances, 1981 (Box 26, Folder 19)
- J.P. Stevens. Ballet Fabrics, Inc., 1983 (Box 26, Folder 20)
- J.P. Stevens Benefit Plan Booklet, 1983 (Box 26, Folder 21)
- J.P. Stevens ACTWU Bulletin, 1980 (Box 26, Folder 22)
  on 1980 Victory
- J.P. Stevens Carter Plant, 1983 (Box 26, Folder 23)
- J.P. Stevens. Allendale, SC, 1981 (Box 26, Folder 24)
- J.P. Stevens. City of Hope, 1980 (Box 26, Folder 25)
  November
- J.P. Stevens Clippings and News, 1980 (Box 26, Folder 26)
- J.P. Stevens Congratulatory Notes, 1980-1983 (Box 26, Folder 27)
  and thank you letters, for 1980 victory
- J.P. Stevens Cotton Dust Hazards, 1983 (Box 26, Folder 28)
- J.P. Stevens Clippings, Comments and Release for 1980 Victory, 1980-1981 (Box 26, Folder 29)
- J.P. Stevens Company Letters, 1980 (Box 26, Folder 30)
  Newspaper Clippings
- J.P. Stevens Clippings, 1981 (Box 26, Folder 31)
- J.P. Stevens Decision of TWUA, 1963 (Box 26, Folder 32)
- J.P. Stevens Clippings, 1982 (Box 26, Folder 33)
- J.P. Stevens Clippings, 1983 (Box 26, Folder 34)
- J.P. Stevens and ACTWU Contract, 1983 (Box 26, Folder 35)
  April; Roanoke Rapids, Allendale, High Point
- J.P. Stevens Negotiations, 1980 (Box 26, Folder 36)
  October 18-19; NYC
- J.P. Stevens Contract Negotiations, 1983 (Box 26, Folder 37)
  News Clippings included
- J.P. Stevens Contract Negotiations, 1985 (Box 26, Folder 38)
- J.P. Stevens Contracts and Agreements, 1980-1985 (Box 26, Folder 39)
- J.P. Stevens Agreement and Contract [Folder 1 of 2], 1980 (Box 26, Folder 40)
- J.P. Stevens Agreement and Contract [Folder 2 of 2], 1980 (Box 26, Folder 41)
- J.P. Stevens. Duneen and Turnersburg, 1981 (Box 26, Folder 42)
- J.P. Stevens. Organizing, 1983 (Box 26, Folder 43)
  East Hampton, MA
- J.P. Stevens East Hampton Massachusetts Plant. Health Hazards, 1980-1982 (Box 26, Folder 44)
- J.P. Stevens Employees Education Committee, 1977-1982 (Box 26, Folder 45)
  Anti-union
- J.P. Stevens. Fayetteville, NC, 1983-1985 (Box 26, Folder 46)
- J.P. Stevens Fayetteville Plant, 1984-1985 (Box 27, Folder 1)
  Report on election held on December 6, 1984
- J.P. Stevens Gay-Tred Mills, 1983 (Box 27, Folder 2)
  Scottsboro, AL
- J.P. Stevens Greensboro. North Carolina Plant, 1982-1983 (Box 27, Folder 3)
- J.P. Stevens Grievance/Arbitration Discussions, 1982 (Box 27, Folder 4)
- J.P. Stevens High Point, 1983 (Box 27, Folder 5)
  North Carolina
- J.P. Stevens. David Hilton, 1982 (Box 27, Folder 6)
  Kingsport, TN
- J.P. Stevens Insurance Charges, 1983 (Box 27, Folder 7)
- The American Lawyer. "Labor Outlaws", 1980 (Box 27, Folder 8)
- J.P. Stevens Legal Matters, 1980-1983 (Box 27, Folder 9)
- J.P. Stevens Mailings. 1980 Victory Material (Box 27, Folder 10)
- J.P. Stevens Milledgeville [Folder 1 of 2], 1979-1980 (Box 27, Folder 11)
- J.P. Stevens Milledgeville [Folder 2 of 2], 1979-1980 (Box 27, Folder 12)
- J.P. Stevens Milledgeville, 1981-1982 (Box 27, Folder 13)
- J.P. Stevens. Miscellaneous, 1982 (Box 27, Folder 14)
- J.P. Stevens. Moran Mills, Ltd., 1983-1984 (Box 27, Folder 15)
  Case #11-RC-5150
- J.P. Stevens. Miscellaneous, 1981 (Box 27, Folder 16)
- J.P. Stevens. Miscellaneous, 1985 (Box 27, Folder 17)
- J.P. Stevens Nation's Labor. Stevens Settlement, 1980 (Box 27, Folder 18)
- J.P. Stevens. New Milford, CT, 1981-1984 (Box 27, Folder 19)
- J.P. Stevens. ACTWU News Releases, 1980-1982 (Box 27, Folder 20)
- J.P. Stevens. Quality Improvement System, 1982 (Box 27, Folder 21)
- J.P. Stevens. West Boylston Plant, 1981-1982 (Box 27, Folder 22)
- J.P. Stevens Tifton, GA Election Petition, 1979-1980 (Box 27, Folder 23)
- J.P. Stevens. Publicity, 1980 (Box 27, Folder 24)
- J.P. Stevens. Rock Hill, SC and Election Proposal, 1981 (Box 27, Folder 25)
  July election
- J.P. Stevens Rosemary Plant, 1982 (Box 27, Folder 26)
- J.P. Stevens. Shareholders' Letters, 1980 (Box 27, Folder 27)
- J.P. Stevens Non-Union Employees Letter. Whitney Stevens, 1980 (Box 27, Folder 28)
- J.P. Stevens. "Social Justice", 1980 (Box 27, Folder 29)
  Last Issue-December
- J.P. Stevens. Sol Stetin's Statement, 1980 (Box 27, Folder 30)
  October 19; NY Hilton
- J.P. Stevens. New Milford, CT, 1978-1980 (Box 27, Folder 31)
- J.P. Stevens Newsletter. Stevens Local Unions' Report, 1983 (Box 27, Folder 32)
- J.P. Stevens ACTWU Press Release [Folder 1 of 2], 1983 (Box 27, Folder 33)
  Release in October; NLRB Settlement after 20 Years
- J.P. Stevens ACTWU Press Release [Folder 2 of 2], 1983 (Box 27, Folder 34)
- J.P. Stevens Plant Closings, 1951-1970 (Box 27, Folder 35)
- J.P. Stevens Stevecoknit Election, 1983 (Box 27, Folder 36)
  Fayetteville, NC; July 28
- J.P. Stevens Stevecoknit, 1982-1983 (Box 27, Folder 37)
  Fayetteville, NC; Bridgeton Dye, Closed
- J.P. Stevens File. "Testimony", 1979 (Box 27, Folder 38)
- J.P. Stevens Closing. Montgomery Yarn Plant Article, 1982 (Box 27, Folder 39)
  Photocopy of article
- J.P. Stevens. Wagram and Roanoke Rapids, 1982 (Box 27, Folder 40)
- J.P. Stevens. Wallace, NC, 1982 (Box 27, Folder 41)
- J.P. Stevens. Wallace, NC, 1980-1985 (Box 27, Folder 42)
- J.P. Stevens. Woolen Division, 1985 (Box 27, Folder 43)
- Roanoke Valley Joint Board, 1981 (Box 27, Folder 44)
  March 29; Roanoke Rapids, NC; Newspaper Clippings included
- J.P. Stevens Newspaper Clippings and Copies, 1979-1983 (Box 27, Folder 45)
- J.P. Stevens. Tifton, GA [Folder 1 of 2], 1981 (Box 27, Folder 46)
- J.P. Stevens. Tifton, GA [Folder 2 of 2], 1981 (Box 27, Folder 47)
- J.P. Stevens Organizing Staff. Staff Training, 1978 (Box 27, Folder 48)
- Mimi Conway. "Rise Gonna Rise", 1979 (Box 27, Folder 49)
- J.P. Stevens New Milford Nonwoven Corporation Agreement. Herbert Haskell, 1981 (Box 27, Folder 50)
- J.P. Stevens. NLRB Cases, 1979-1982 (Box 27, Folder 51)
- J.P. Stevens Court Cases [Folder 1 of 4], 1975-1986 (Box 28, Folder 1)
- J.P. Stevens Court Cases [Folder 2 of 4], 1975-1986 (Box 28, Folder 2)
- J.P. Stevens Court Cases [Folder 3 of 4], 1975-1986 (Box 28, Folder 3)
- J.P. Stevens Court Cases [Folder 4 of 4], 1975-1986 (Box 28, Folder 4)
- Newsletters, 1985-1987 (Box 28, Folder 5)
- IUD Conference. "Threat of the Radical Right Wing in America", 1978 (Box 28, Folder 6)
  August 29-30; Washington D.C.
- AFL-CIO IUD Executive Committee. To Recommend Future Directions and Activities of the IUD, 1975-1976 (Box 28, Folder 7)
- Glenn Watts Confidential Statement. IUD Committee on Future, 1977 (Box 28, Folder 8)
- Glenn Watts File Copy of Draft of Statement for IUD, 1977 (Box 28, Folder 9)
  Chairman of Future Directions Committee
- UTW Josepha Krause Autobiography. 1975 Conviction Data, 1973-1982 (Box 28, Folder 10)
- UTW Recommendations from Jack Rubenstein, 1979 (Box 28, Folder 11)
  March; Retired V.P.
- United Textile Workers, 1979-1986 (Box 28, Folder 12)
- United Textile Workers. AFL-CIO, 1968-1973 (Box 28, Folder 13)
- IUD AFL-CIO Various Committees, 1978 (Box 28, Folder 14)
- IUD Organizing Committee Meeting. Lists of Companies, 1978 (Box 28, Folder 15)
  Distributed at August 28 Meeting
- IUD Organizing Meeting and SCLC Convention, 1984 (Box 28, Folder 16)
  August 16; Charlotte, NC
- IUD Organizing Committee Meeting, 1979 (Box 28, Folder 17)
  August 21; Washington D.C.
- IUD Oversight Committee on Organizing, 1979 (Box 28, Folder 18)
- IUD Organizing Oversight Committee Meetings Minutes, 1978-1979 (Box 28, Folder 19)
- IUD Oversight Organizing Committee, 1978-1979 (Box 28, Folder 20)
  January 16; Washington D.C.
- IUD AFL-CIO Organizing Committee [Folder 1 of 2], 1978 (Box 28, Folder 21)
- IUD AFL-CIO Organizing Committee [Folder 2 of 2], 1978 (Box 28, Folder 22)
- IUD AFL-CIO Organizing Committee Meeting, 1978 (Box 28, Folder 23)
  August 28; Washington, D.C.
- Shipment of Archive Materials to Cornell, 1996 (Box 28, Folder 24)
  February 14
- IUD Minutes, 1979 (Box 28, Folder 25)
- IUD Carlin Allen. Organizing, 1980 (Box 28, Folder 26)
- IUD Cooperative Organizing Programs in Carolinas, 1984 (Box 28, Folder 27)
- IUD Atlanta Coordinated Organizing Project, 1981-1982 (Box 28, Folder 28)
  July 1981
- IUD Elmer Chatak. Secretary-Treasurer, 1980 (Box 28, Folder 29)
- IUD Howard Samuel. Miscellaneous, 1979-1984 (Box 28, Folder 30)
  President
- Reports to IUD Executive Committee on J.P. Stevens Campaign, 1977 (Box 28, Folder 31)
- IUD Harold McIver. Organizational Director, 1979-1985 (Box 28, Folder 32)
- IUD Miscellaneous, 1978-1980 (Box 28, Folder 33)
  Newspaper Clipping included
- IUD North Alabama-Mississippi Project, 1980 (Box 28, Folder 34)
- IUD Coordinated Organizing Program, 1980-1984 (Box 28, Folder 35)
  Tupelo, MS
- IUD Coordinated Bargaining Committee Kendall Company. Colgate-Palmolive Subsidiary, 1980 (Box 28, Folder 36)
- National Democratic Party Mid Term Conference, 1978 (Box 28, Folder 37)
  December 8-10; Memphis, TN
- National Health Plan, 1970-1976 (Box 28, Folder 38)
- National Housing Conference, Inc., 1976-1979 (Box 28, Folder 39)
- Nation's Labor, 1972-1978 (Box 28, Folder 40)
- National Trade Union Council For Human Rights, 1971-1978 (Box 28, Folder 41)
- National Urban League, Inc., 1974-1976 (Box 28, Folder 42)
- New York Committee for Labor Youth, 1974-1976 (Box 28, Folder 43)
- New York State Department of Labor, 1978 (Box 28, Folder 44)
- New York Diagnostic Center, 1976 (Box 28, Folder 45)
- New York State AFL-CIO. Sy Cohen COPE Director, 1975-1978 (Box 28, Folder 46)
- New York State Assembly, 1975-1977 (Box 28, Folder 47)
- New York State Democratic Committee, 1976-1978 (Box 28, Folder 48)
- Paul Swaity. Director of Organizing, 1978 (Box 28, Folder 49)
- Paul Swaity. Director of Organizing [Folder 1 of 2], 1976-1977 (Box 29, Folder 1)
- Paul Swaity. Director of Organizing [Folder 2 of 2], 1976-1977 (Box 29, Folder 2)
- Paul Swaity. Election Memos [Folder 1 of 2], 1976-1978 (Box 29, Folder 3)
- Paul Swaity. Election Memos [Folder 2 of 2], 1976-1978 (Box 29, Folder 4)
- Miscellaneous: Opinions, Open Doors and Ohio AFL-CIO, 1974-1978 (Box 29, Folder 5)
- OSHA. Society for Occupational and Environmental Health [Folder 1 of 2], 1976-1978 (Box 29, Folder 6)
- OSHA. Society for Occupational and Environmental Health [Folder 2 of 2], 1976-1978 (Box 29, Folder 7)
- Reunion of Old Timers, 1974-1976 (Box 29, Folder 8)
- Organizational Expenses, 1976 (Box 29, Folder 9)
- Miscellaneous: Princeton, Pension and Patton, 1972-1978 (Box 29, Folder 10)
- Panama Canal Treaties, 1978 (Box 29, Folder 11)
- Political Action Committee. Material from Politicians, 1975-1978 (Box 29, Folder 12)
- Public Policy Conference, 1978 (Box 29, Folder 13)
  May 14-26; Aspen, CO
- Textile Workers' Pension Fund. William Gordon Correspondence, 1976-1977 (Box 29, Folder 14)
  Secretary-Treasurer
- Textile Workers' Pension Fund [Folder 1 of 2], 1978-1979 (Box 29, Folder 15)
- Textile Workers' Pension Fund [Folder 2 of 2], 1978-1979 (Box 29, Folder 16)
- Textile Workers' Pension Fund. William DuChessi [Folder 1 of 3], 1977-1978 (Box 29, Folder 17)
  Trustee
- Textile Workers' Pension Fund. William DuChessi [Folder 2 of 3], 1977-1978 (Box 29, Folder 18)
- Textile Workers' Pension Fund. William DuChessi [Folder 3 of 3], 1977-1978 (Box 29, Folder 19)
- Textile Workers' Pension Fund. William DuChessi [Folder 1 of 3], 1976 (Box 29, Folder 20)
- Textile Workers' Pension Fund. William DuChessi [Folder 2 of 3], 1976 (Box 29, Folder 21)
- Textile Workers' Pension Fund. William DuChessi [Folder 3 of 3], 1976 (Box 29, Folder 22)
- Christmas. Lists, Sample Cards, Memos, Etc., 1972-1975 (Box 29, Folder 23)
- Communications Workers of America, 1973-1978 (Box 29, Folder 24)
  Joseph Beirne, President
- Congressional Hispanic Caucus, 1976-1978 (Box 29, Folder 25)
- Congressional Records, 1974-1977 (Box 29, Folder 26)
- Concerned Seniors for Better Government, 1974-1976 (Box 30, Folder 1)
  Matthew DeMore, Chairman
- Congress of the United States [Folder 1 of 2], 1976-1979 (Box 30, Folder 2)
- Congress of the United States [Folder 2 of 2], 1976-1979 (Box 30, Folder 3)
- Conso Products, 1975-1976 (Box 30, Folder 4)
- Cornell University, 1979 (Box 30, Folder 5)
- COPE. General, 1976-1978 (Box 30, Folder 6)
- Contribution to Labor College, 1971-1977 (Box 30, Folder 7)
- 28th Annual COPE. Legislative Institute, 1977 (Box 30, Folder 8)
  Burlington Hotel, Washington D.C.; March 20-25
- COPE Legislative Conference, 1976 (Box 30, Folder 9)
  March 21-26; Washington D.C.
- New York State COPE Seminar, 1977 (Box 30, Folder 10)
  June 3-5; State University of NY Albany Campus
- Memos and Copies of Correspondence [Folder 1 of 2], 1976-1977 (Box 30, Folder 11)
- Memos and Copies of Correspondence [Folder 2 of 2], 1976-1977 (Box 30, Folder 12)
- Copies of Correspondence, 1976 (Box 30, Folder 13)
- Copies of Correspondence, 1976 (Box 30, Folder 14)
- Copies of Correspondence, 1976 (Box 30, Folder 15)
- Copies of Correspondence, 1976 (Box 30, Folder 16)
  September
- Copies of Correspondence, 1976 (Box 30, Folder 17)
- Copies of Correspondence, 1976 (Box 30, Folder 18)
- Copies of Correspondence, 1976 (Box 30, Folder 19)
- Copies of Correspondence, 1976 (Box 30, Folder 20)
  May
- Copies of Correspondence, 1976 (Box 30, Folder 21)
- Copies of Correspondence, 1976 (Box 30, Folder 22)
- Copies of Correspondence, 1976 (Box 30, Folder 23)
  January
- Careers. Requests for ACTWU Information, 1977 (Box 30, Folder 24)
- Requests for Contributions. General, 1977-1978 (Box 30, Folder 25)
- Miscellaneous: Democratic, Departments and Directory, 1974-1978 (Box 30, Folder 26)
- Data Packet for TWUA Locals, 1969 (Box 30, Folder 27)
- Department Head Meetings, 1969-1978 (Box 30, Folder 28)
- "Dissent", 1970 (Box 30, Folder 29)
- Delinquent Per Capita and Monthly Cash Reports, 1976-1979 (Box 30, Folder 30)
- Dues Paying Membership, 1976 (Box 30, Folder 31)
- Bruce Dunton, 1976-1977 (Box 30, Folder 32)
- Defense Fund. Correspondence, 1976-1977 (Box 30, Folder 33)
- Defense Fund. Strike Authorization, 1976-1977 (Box 30, Folder 34)
- Defense Fund. Strike Payments, 1976-1977 (Box 30, Folder 35)